Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- Civic and social organizations
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Ladies’ Auxiliary outdoor supper, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 36)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - American Legion Hall and workers, 1938 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 696)
    - Cannon Grange - Miscellaneous, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 623)
    - Cannon Grange - Activities, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 837)
    - Cannon Grange - Drill Team, 1898 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 390)
    - Cannon Grange - Milk maids in costume, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 391)
    - Comstock Fife and Drum Corps, 1979 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 666)
    - Drum Hill - Daughters of the American Revolution marker, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 782)
    - Hall of Volunteers, 1981 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 194)
    - Comstock Community Center, 1999 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 911)
    - Kiwanians Breaking Ground / "Y", 1971 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 793)
    - Liberty Bond Drive, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 84)
    - Rolling Hills Country Club, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 326)
    - Town Hall - Garden Club, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 137)
    - Wilton Athletic Club, circa 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 833)
    - Wilton Choral Club, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 314)
- Entertainment, recreation, and sports
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Women’s drill team, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 25)
    - Women with tennis racquets, undated; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 4)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Ambler Farm Day, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 329)
    - Cannondale Gardens, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 930)
    - Croquet game, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 872)
    - Fishing, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 619)
    - Horse Show, 1910 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 186)
    - Fire Department - Minstrel Show, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 652)
    - Railroad play scenery, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 540)
    - Schenck's Island Park, 2000 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 946)
    - Summer Outing, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 608)
    - Swimming class, circa 1937 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 864)
    - Swimming pool in millstream, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 437)
    - Tercentenary Play, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 498)
    - Weir Preserve Nature Walks, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 823)
    - Wild Duck Open Space, 1967 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 295)
    - Wilton Farmers baseball team, 1923 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 644)
    - Wilton Riding Club, circa 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 858)
    - Wilton swim team, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 239)
    - Wilton tennis players, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 385)
- Government and services
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Old Town Hall, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 66)
    - Wilton Post Office, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 30)
    - Rural free mail delivery, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 13)
    - Wilton Post Office, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 16)
    - Wilton’s original Town Hall, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 26)
    - Old Town Hall, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 47)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Fire Department dinner, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 169)
    - Fire Department trucks and ambulance, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 181)
    - Fire Department volunteer, 1959 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 842)
    - Georgetown Fire Engine no. 3, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 462)
    - Georgetown Post Office and Railroad Station, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 941)
    - Hurlbutt Street Post Office, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 132)
    - New Town Hall, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 134)
    - Old Post Office, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 135)
    - Police Department, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 921)
    - Post Office Green, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 130)
    - South Wilton Post Office, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 131)
    - Town Hall complex, 1999 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 913)
    - Wilton Post Office, circa 1940 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 677)
    - Wilton postal workers, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 832)
- Historic buildings, landmarks, and scenery
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Wilton - Scenes and people, 1989; This is a box of slides. This item is MISSING. (Box 787, Item *)
    - Norwalk River and “long-johns”, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 27)
    - Wilton Library, undated; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 3)
    - Wilton Library - Interior, undated; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 1)
    - Harre, John C. - Post Office Square, Wilton Center, 1951; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 10)
    - Harre, John C. - Wilton Academy and Town Hall, 1820; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 4)
    - Harre, John C. - Wilton Meeting House, 1790; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 3)
    - Wilton in the 1950s - Georgetown, This is a box of slides. Includes an identification notebook. (Box SL-1, Item *)
    - Wilton in the 1950s - Miscellaneous scenes, This is a box of slides. (Box SL-2, Item *)
    - Wilton in the 1950s - Old postcards, This is a box of slides. (Box SL-3, Item *)
    - “Then and Now in Wilton”, undated; Slide program produced by Jim Fannon and Art Goldsmith for “Wilton Dearest” lobby exhibition, held in 1990. (Box SL-4, Item *)
    - “Old Time Wilton,” part I, undated; Slide program produced by Augustus Merwin from old photographs. (Box SL-5a, Item *)
    - “Old Time Wilton,” part II, undated; Slide program produced by Augustus Merwin from old photographs. (Box SL-5b, Item *)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Squires, Mac - Murals of Wilton Center, 1962 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 973)
    - Along a Wilton Road - Drawing, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 637)
    - Wilton Library, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 7)
    - DeForest, W. - Early Wilton, circa 1899 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 822)
    - DeForest, W. - Early Wilton and Georgetown, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 841)
    - Harre, John C. - Postcards, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 797)
    - Harre, John C. - Town Hall and Wilton Academy, 1850; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 25)
    - Harre, John C. - Upper Reservoir, undated; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 42)
    - Harre, John C. Harre - Turner's Ridge, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 638)
    - Historic buildings - Postcard collection, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 218)
    - Allen's Meadow, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 892)
    - Negatives - P1 through P40, undated; Contains old photographs of Wilton, including prominent buildings, houses, landmarks, scenery, and people (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 40)
    - At the seashore, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 636)
    - Bald Hill - Old chestnut tree, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 23)
    - Wilton Center – Painting of fire, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 959)
    - Bald Hill - View, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 31)
    - Belden Hill - Norwalk Reservoir, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 408)
    - Belden Hill - Winter scene, 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 44)
    - Bryant's Brook - Winter scene, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 47)
    - Buildings - Unidentified, circa 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 590)
    - Cannon Crossing - Buildings, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 626)
    - Cannondale Brook, 1912; Includes photographs and negatives. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 605)
    - Chicken Street - Boulder, 1901 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 4)
    - Chicken Street - Cave, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 5)
    - Drum Hill Reservoir, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 27)
    - Earth Day, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 33)
    - Fitches Corner, Main Road, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 727)
    - Fox Meadows - Oak trees, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 38)
    - Georgetown, 1998 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 963)
    - Georgetown Gorge, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 281)
    - Georgetown scenes, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 255)
    - Graenest Ridge - Springtime in Wilton, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 28)
    - Historic trees, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 784)
    - Huckleberry Woods - Mineral Spring, 1849 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 3)
    - Kent Pond, circa 1986 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 142)
    - Merwin Falls - Frozen, 1892 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 13)
    - Merwin Meadows, circa 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 680)
    - Miller Hall, Georgetown, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 172)
    - Nod Hill and Olmstead Hill area, 1913 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 52)
    - Nod Lake, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 861)
    - Norwalk River, 1930; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 43)
    - Norwalk River, South Wilton, 1908 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 85)
    - Norwalk River, Wilton Center, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 411)
    - Old elm tree, undated; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous postcards, undated; Locations shown are unidentified. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 825)
    - Old Georgetown, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 678)
    - Pope's Pond, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 35)
    - Scene near Cannon Station, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 616)
    - Scenes of Wilton, 1970s; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 576)
    - Silver Mine, Mather Street, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 182)
    - Snow scenes, 1920s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 935)
    - South Norwalk Reservoir, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 89)
    - Split Rock, Cannondale, 1888 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 283)
    - United States - Scenery, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 550)
    - Warncke's Hill - View, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 601)
    - West view of Wilton, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 633)
    - Wilton Center, 1940s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 294)
    - Wilton Center, circa 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 811)
    - Wilton Center - Aerial views, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 566)
    - Wilton Center - Aerial views, 1949 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 914)
    - Wilton Center - Buildings, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 938)
    - Wilton winter, 1915 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 34)
    - Winter scene, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 448)
    - Woods near South Wilton, 1958 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 82)
- Miscellaneous
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Wilton adopts adaptive use, Newtown Bee, 1973; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Folder 5, 6)
    - Gould, Marilyn - "A light look at Wilton history", 1987; This is a box of slides; it includes a script. (Box SL-10, Item *)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Johnson, Karl - Artwork, undated; File includes negatives and original artwork. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 543)
    - Sherman, Huldah - Sampler, 1842 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 950)
    - Thomson, Henry - Artwork, undated; File includes photographs of original artwork. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 306)
    - Wilton Arts Council Festival, 1979 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 755)
    - Works Progress Administration murals, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 237)
    - Works Progress Authority mural at Hurlbutt Apple Orchard, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 785)
    - Works Progress Authority mural at Scribner Roadside stand, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 786)
    - World War Two - Airplane spotting station, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 301)
    - Ambulance drive, undated; This file contains images of a fundraiser to pay for an ambulance. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 780)
    - Town Poor at the house of R. W. Keeler, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 289)
    - Branchville Railroad Station - Tenement house, 1978 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 293)
    - Cannondale cannon, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 628)
    - Civil Defense truck on Cottage Row, 1957 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 891)
    - Kensett Sanitarium, South Wilton, 1958 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 83)
    - Revolutionary War - King George III statue, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 536)
    - Revolutionary War - King George III statue, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 302)
    - Revolutionary War - King George III statue pieces, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 881)
    - Revolutionary War - Map of General William Tryon's raid, 1946 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 546)
    - Wilton Calendar, 1965; Twelve month calendar of photographs of Wilton. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 500)
    - Wilton Calendar, 1967; Twelve month calendar of photographs of Wilton. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 547)
    - Politicians in Wilton, 1958 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 838)
    - Republican Party election, 1976 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 568)
    - Town Hall, aerial view, circa 1935 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 975)
    - Wilton boundary sign, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 926)
    - Wilton Home Guard, 1940 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 906)
    - Wilton, England, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 534)
- Roads and transportation
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Cannondale Railroad Station, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 32)
    - Cannondale Railroad Station with teacher and students, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 31)
    - Intersection of Ridgefield and Belden Hill Roads, 1890; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 9)
    - Old Bridge at Lovers Lane, circa 1920; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 61)
    - Old Wilton Railroad Station, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 62)
    - Railroad crossing on Seeley Road with train, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 22)
    - Cannondale Railroad Station, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 32)
    - Wilton Railroad Station - Original station, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 14)
    - Hurlbutt Street - Turn-of-the-century view, circa 1900; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 5)
    - Railroad Station, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 49a, 49b)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - 31 Old Ridgefield Road, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 934)
    - Benedict bus at Big Elm Farm, circa 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 713)
    - Branchville Railroad Station, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 654)
    - Buggy ride, 1952 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 602)
    - Buggy ride, 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 715)
    - Cannon Railroad Station, 1907 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 88)
    - Hurlbutt, Lewis - Touring car, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 700)
    - Crossroads at Wilton Congregational Church, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 154)
    - Dana Railroad Station, 1975; This file contains photographs of the Old Wilton Railroad Station, after its removal to Charles Dana's property. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 688)
    - Danbury and Norwalk Railroad, 1967 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 549)
    - Danbury and Norwalk Railroad locomotive, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 581)
    - Danbury Railroad Station, 1912 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 868)
    - Danbury Road, unpaved, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 53)
    - Davenport Woods, Graenest Road, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 49)
    - Elevated railroad - Tracks and trestle, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 587)
    - First bus in Wilton, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 573)
    - Hurlbutt Street, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 56)
    - Hurlbutt Street - View, 1908 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 127)
    - Intersection of Route 7 and Route 33, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 936)
    - Intersection of Route 7 and Wolfpit, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 545)
    - Lovers Lane, 1901 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 6)
    - Middlebrook Farm Road - Turner's Ridge, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 37)
    - Milestones, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 93)
    - Motoring in the countryside, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 51)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 582)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 583)
    - Newtown Turnpike - Boulder, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 681)
    - Old Danbury Road - Poison Rock, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 39)
    - Old Mill Road / Peckham Bridge, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 55)
    - Old Ridgefield Road, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 687)
    - Old Wilton bridges, circa 1890 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 790)
    - Ox cart, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 657)
    - Pittsfield Express Railroad, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 497)
    - Portrait of a coachman, 1893 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 788)
    - Railroad car interior, 1939 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 447)
    - Railroad locomotive, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 621)
    - Railroad stop at Kent Road, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 539)
    - Railroad track raising at Norwalk, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 584)
    - Railroad tracks in Norwalk, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 588)
    - Railroad turntable and tracks, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 586)
    - Ridgefield Road showing dirt and elm trees, 1929 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 50)
    - Ridgefield Road view, circa 1960 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 698)
    - Roads and Old Mill, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 212)
    - Route 7 in front of Town Hall, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 494)
    - Route 7 widening, circa 1926 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 948)
    - South Norwalk Railroad Station, 1895 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 585)
    - South Wilton Railroad Station, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 22)
    - Wilton Center Railroad Station, 1939 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 21)
    - Wilton Center Railroad Station, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 19, 20)
    - Wilton Railroad Station, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 128)
    - Wilton Railroad Station, 1951 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 436)
    - Wilton Railroad Station, 1977 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 541)
    - Wilton Railroad Station, 1917 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 783)
    - Wilton Railroad Station and bridge, circa 1913 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 277)
    - Wilton Railroad Station by Smith, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 580)
    - Wilton Road to Old Railroad Station, 1915 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 41)
- Schools
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Bald Hill School, with students, undated; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 2)
    - Belden Hill School, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 15)
    - Center School District no. 4, on intersection of Belden Hill and Drum Hill, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 4)
    - Hurlbutt Street School, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 46)
    - Lockwood-Brown Academy - 33 Cannon Road, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 42)
    - Middlebrook School on Olmstead Hill with teacher, Blanche Smith, and students, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 1)
    - Nod Hill School, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 35)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Bald Hill School, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 63)
    - Bald Hill School and students, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 91)
    - Bald Hill School students, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 719)
    - Belden Hill School, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 57)
    - Belden Hill School, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 72)
    - Belden Hill School, 1908; This file includes negatives. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 544)
    - Belden Hill School - 424 Belden Hill Road, 1985 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 79)
    - Cannon Crossing School, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 625)
    - Cannon Station School, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 68)
    - Cannondale Railroad Station with students, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 684)
    - Cannondale School, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 45)
    - Cannondale School with students, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 58)
    - Center School, 1918 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 73)
    - Center School, circa 1930; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 819)
    - Center School basement murals, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 598)
    - Center School students, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 717)
    - Center School teacher, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 71)
    - Center School, Class of 1962, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 117)
    - Chestnut Hill School and students, undated; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 60)
    - Cider Mill School, 1999 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 912)
    - Danbury Normal School, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 65)
    - Danbury Normal School, 1907 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 974)
    - Driscoll School, 1970s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 110)
    - Gilbert and Bennett School, 1920; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 66)
    - Gilbert and Bennett School - Classes, 1910 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 67)
    - Hurlbutt Street School, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 61)
    - Hurlbutt Street School - Interior, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 682)
    - Hurlbutt Street School with students, circa 1960 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 641)
    - Kent School, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 62, 77)
    - Leatherland, Alice and students, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 593)
    - 33 Lovers Lane - Wilton Academy, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 873)
    - Middlebrook School, 1928 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 59)
    - Middlebrook School class, 1897 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 690)
    - Middlebrook School construction, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 662)
    - Middlebrook School with students, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 634)
    - Miller School class, 1970 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 14)
    - Nod Hill School, 1985 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 64)
    - Nod Hill School interior, 1927 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 844)
    - Nod Hill School students, circa 1880 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 653)
    - Norwalk High School, 1905 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 817)
    - Norwalk High School graduating class, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 502)
    - Old Georgetown School and students, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 617)
    - School Districts nos. 1 to 10, undated; This file includes slides. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 904)
    - School with students in Weston, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 226)
    - Wilton High School, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 574)
    - Wilton Junior High School, 1949 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 113)